Kaz Gosho

Full Stack Web Engineer

Efficient and skilled in web application creation with a diverse knowledge of web technologies, I have been a web engineer for 6 years. I have garnered a multitude experiences in the field of Server-side and Front-end programming, Front-end building, SQL tuning and others. I am also familiar with Infrastructure & DevOps tools such as AWS, CircleCI and Docker.

Japanese, English	+8180-7808-4235	ketsume0211@gmail.com	Tokyo, Japan
Languages	Phone Number	Email	Location

Work Experience

Self Employed 2

2018.04 ~ Current

Presidenet

I solve various kind of technical problems as an independen consultunt.

- AWS managemnet (EC2, RDS, ElastiCache, ECS, Lambda, CloudFront, CloudWatch, etc.)
- React + Almin
- Improve React Native app working flow using Fastlane
- Create React Native tutorial for Programming education company
- Consult business strategy for startups

Traimmu.inc

2017.03 ~ 2018.04

Lead Engineer

I work on broadening the scale of our web application (https://www.in-fra.jp). When I first joined the company, the application was a little outdated in both infrastructure and code, so our major task is refactoring the program. I've decreased application's TTFB by 2000ms.

- Replace ¡Query with Vue.js
- Refactor Laravel source code
- Create iOS App with React Native
- Change the infrastructure from Heroku to AWS EC2
- Improve deployment process using Ansible on CircleCI
- o Implement easy setup development environment Docker
- Visualize business KPI with Metabase
- SQL tuning

Quick CO., LTD.

2015.04 ~ 2017.02

Sales (2015.04 ~ 09), Engineer (2015.10 ~ 2017.02)

I worked in sales first half a year. In the sales department, I made appointments with new customers, and secured contracts with them. Then I moved to the engineering department, where I conducted maintenance on internal systems.

- Sale of Human Resource solutions
- Create new functions with FuelPHP
- Build systems

OSS Contributions

- fzf https://github.com/junegunn/fzf
 - Fix a bug for FishShell
- ActiveHash https://github.com/zilkey/active_hash
 - Fix documentation mistype
- enhancd https://github.com/b4b4r07/enhancd
 - Add new functions
- xremap https://github.com/k0kubun/xremap
 - Fix a bug for Awesome Window Manager

Development Skills

- Linux (5 years)
- PHP (5 years)
- HTML, CSS (5 years)
- Laravel (2 years)
- JavaScript, ECMAScript (2 years)
- SQL (2 years)
- AWS, CircleCI, GitHub (2 years)
- Node.js (1 year)
- Vue.js (1 year)
- React, React Native (1 year)
- Docker (1 year)

Profile Links

- https://github.com/acro5piano
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/kay-gosho-587a05121
- https://acro5piano.github.io
- https://dev.to/acro5piano
- https://qiita.com/acro5piano (Japanese website)

• Fix bugs and prevent system degradation

Education

Hitotsubashi University 2011.04 ~ 2015.03

Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics

- Programming
- Linear Algebra, Calculus
- Statistics